- Thank you, Elena.
- Mm-hm.
I've decided to
redo the living room.
The living room is fine.
Cecil assured me that if
he gets started right away,
he'll have it done in
time for the wedding.
We're not redoing
the living room, Sarah.
Cecil is coming here
first thing in the morning.
I will not allow that
man or anyone else
to waste my money
indulging your silly whims.
The living room is a dump.
The living room is fine.
It was your idea to
hold the reception...
I said no! No!
You hear me? No!
Cecil wants to go
with teal this time.
Teal, salmon and beige.
He can't wait to get rid of
that hideous burgundy carpet.
You enjoy doing
this to me, don't you?
Doing what, darling?
I spend ten hours a day at the
office with my stomach in knots,
trying to keep my competitors
from eating me alive,
and what do I get when I
come home? More aggravation.
More aggravation and
a splitting headache.
Damn you, Sarah.
Damn you.
Justin. Oh, my God.
Elena, call 911. Something's
happened to Justin.
Oh, my God.
Well, I'll be.
What?
Justin Kerns died last night.
Keeled over at dinner. Stroke.
Friend of yours?
No. I used to run into
him once in a while.
Morning.
- Front door was open.
- Hi. Come on in.
- You want some coffee?
- Uh...
No. Oh, I see you've
already got the paper.
- Want the comics?
- No, already read them.
What are you doing?
I'm looking to see
what page you're on.
Why?
Ahem. Because, uh,
before you get to Page 15,
you gotta let me
explain something.
No, just don't go
right, Ben. Don't...
"For all your legal needs, call
Clifford R. Lewis, attorney-at-law.
Your local legal beagle."
Cute picture, Cliff. Whose dogs?
My neighbors'.
You ran an ad.
- Yeah, but it was...
- I hate it when lawyers run ads.
- I know. I do too.
- It's demeaning, undignified.
- It was my father's idea.
- Oh.
He thought it was time that I
started acting more like a lawyer
instead of a glorified law
clerk. His words, not mine.
You don't wanna
work with us anymore?
Oh, yeah. Oh, I do.
Oh, absolutely, I do.
It's just that I wanna
work for myself too.
In fact, I've got a meeting with
a potential client this morning.
- Malpractice suit.
- Your ad paid off already?
Well, actually,
my picture paid off.
This lady said that I was
strong- and dependable-looking.
Cliff, are you sure
you wanna do this?
Gotta try it sometime.
But there's a lot you don't know.
- Yeah.
A lot that doesn't have
anything to do with law.
- I know. MATLOCK:
There are courtroom tricks
that you can pull that can
swing the verdict your way.
Ben... You don't
know those tricks.
I know. I just gotta try
sometime. Ben, I just gotta try.
Okay.
Well, Leanne, I guess we'll
be out of business pretty soon.
A simple blepharoplasty,
that's all I wanted.
A what?
- Oh, eye job.
- Oh.
My upper lids were sagging,
and my lower ones were puffy.
He said he could fix them.
Well, he fixed them, all right.
Look at them now.
They look okay to me.
Oh, you're just being polite.
- No. Really, they...
- You've gotta look closer.
Come here.
Now, look again and
be brutally honest.
I can take it.
I do see little lines
here and there.
Little lines?
Those are full-fledged
wrinkles, and you know it.
And they were not there before
that butcher operated on me.
Are you sure?
Well, yeah. Um,
well, see for yourself.
Now, here.
Now, that was me
less than two years ago.
Do you see any wrinkles?
Well, no, but the picture's
kind of out of focus.
Oh, that's because
my idiot husband took it.
Are you divorced?
He dumped me for
a younger woman.
But I fixed him.
I took him and his hyperactive
libido for every cent he had.
Do you know what?
He not only gave me wrinkles,
he made my eyes smaller.
I mean, look at this.
See how large my eyes are
here, and look at them now.
Look how small they are now.
Well, actually, you
know, you just...
You look a little
older, that's all, heh.
- That's all?
- Yeah.
That's all?
Ahh, that's what I mean.
Instead of making me look
younger, he made me look older.
I can't live like this.
He's butchered me.
Mrs. Westmore,
you know, I really, I...
Oh, please,
call me Jackie.
Jackie.
I think you need a more
experienced lawyer.
Oh, no, Cliff, no.
What I need is a lawyer
who's young and hungry
and willing to fight to
the death for a just cause.
- I don't even know that we have a...
- Cliff.
Case. Yes?
You can do it.
What's the name of the plastic
surgeon that butchered you?
Levinson.
Albert Levinson.
What do you think?
About what?
Can you do it?
Of course I can
do it, but, uh...
How soon?
Well, surely, the question
must be "How much?"
Money's no object, doctor.
I'll pay you up front
in full and in cash.
Well, in that case, I think we can
probably schedule you in right away.
Want me to fix the
hairline while I'm at it?
Oh, yeah.
Dr. Levinson.
Can you come out here for a
minute, please? It's important.
Oh. Yes. Excuse
me. Be right back.
This was just delivered.
You're being sued.
- Oh, not again.
- Yeah.
- Who?
- Jackie Westmore.
Ahh. For crying out loud,
she's a total flake. She's nuts.
She may be a flake,
but she's got a lawyer
who's gonna take you to court.
Damn.
Ahem. As the judge has explained
to all of you potential jurors,
this case involves
plastic surgery.
How do you feel about plastic
surgery, uh, Mr. Webster?
I don't know.
It's okay, I guess.
Have, um...? Have you ever,
uh, undergone plastic surgery?
No. CLIFF: Have you ever
thought about
undergoing plastic surgery?
- No.
- Why not?
Oh. Oh, no, no, no. Oh, no.
No, not that I was implying,
uh, that you need plastic surgery,
I was merely trying to, uh,
discern your attitude towards it.
My attitude is I like
myself just the way I am,
and if other people don't like
it, well, that's their tough luck.
Well, how do you feel about
people who have nose jobs
or have their eyes done?
Uh, oh, um...
Your Honor, may I
just have one moment?
Excuse me.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm passing by.
Listen, this guy doesn't
like you. Write him off.
I know, but I figure if I don't
make him like me, he's gonna...
It'll make things worse.
Write him off. Move on.
- Ben, I think that I know what I'm...
- Cliff, write him off.
No further questions, Your
Honor. Uh, pass for cause.
You're dismissed.
Oh, Cliff, you're doing so well.
Elena, what are you doing
with Mr. Kerns' clothes?
How dare you? Put
those back immediately.
But, Mrs. Kerns, your
daughter told me...
I know what you're up to, Elena.
I'm no fool. Now, put them back.
- Oh, Mrs. Kerns.
- Mother, what's going on?
Elena is fired.
I just caught her sneaking
Justin's things out of the closet.
No doubt she was
going to sell them.
I was just doing what
you asked me to do, Miss...
I know, I know,
Elena. It's okay.
Now, just go downstairs.
Makes me wonder what
else is missing around here.
Ahh, Mother, she was
following my orders.
I told her to clean out Father's
clothes so we could give them to charity.
Without consulting me?
I thought it might upset you.
What upsets me is you sneaking
around my back all the time.
His things are my
things now, young lady.
I'll decide what's to be done
with them. Do you hear me?
Yes, Mother, now just relax.
Did you take your pill today?
That's none of your business.
- Mother.
Why aren't you at work?
Because my car broke down.
I had to have it
towed to the garage.
I need a new car.
Just get this one fixed and
then don't drive it so much.
That's all you young people do
nowadays is drive, drive, drive.
Father left you
millions of dollars.
All I'm asking for is
20-, maybe 25,000.
Your father didn't
work himself to death
just to indulge your
every silly whim.
Silly whim? I've had that
car for nearly ten years.
First you want a big wedding.
Now you want a new car.
Next you'll want a house.
I want a new car, Mother. - No.
- I need a new car.
- N-O. No.
- Struck out, huh?
- Surprise, surprise.
Just take me back to the office.
All right.
When do those things come off?
Two more days.
Good.
And you've been
Dr. Levinson's scrub nurse
- for how long?
- Seven years.
So when he moved his practice
from Dallas, you moved with him?
That's right.
He's not just a
brilliant surgeon,
he's also a wonderful
man to work for.
Uh, objection, non-response.
Sustained.
Just answer the
question, please.
Don't editorialize.
I'm sorry.
Would you identify these
photos for us, please?
Certainly.
The first one is a photo
Dr. Levinson took of Jackie Westmore
the day before
her blepharoplasty.
And that one he took several
weeks after the procedure.
You are somewhat of
an expert on this subject.
How would you rate the results?
Well, the suture lines
are all but invisible.
There's no
puckering of the lids.
No unevenness of skin tone.
It's a masterful job,
very typical of Dr. Levinson's
work. It's always excellent.
Objection.
Sustained.
You're doing it again.
I'm sorry.
You've helped Dr. Levinson perform
this procedure on exactly 97 patients.
- Have you not?
- Sounds right.
And exactly 96 of
them were satisfied?
Yes, they were.
In fact, they
weren't just satisfied,
they were delighted,
were they not?
Objection.
Leading the witness.
Sustained.
Mr. Matlock, Mr. Lewis,
approach the bench.
- Cut it out.
- Cut what out?
Coaching Mr. Lewis
from the gallery.
Why, Your Honor...
Mr. Lewis wears long pants,
appears to shave, and
his voice has changed.
So I must assume
he has a law degree
and is old enough to
argue his own case.
- Um, Your Honor...
- Did I ask for you to speak?
No, Your Honor.
Mr. Matlock, cut out the cough.
Oh, Your Honor, I
have this little tickle.
Stifle the tickle or get
out of the courtroom.
Do you understand?
Ahem. Your Honor, may I speak?
Yes, Mr. Lewis.
Your Honor, if I might have a
minute with Mr. Matlock out in the hall,
I think that I might be able
to help him with his tickle.
Do that, Mr. Lewis.
And if Mr. Matlock's
tickle persists,
both of you may be
headed to the hoosegow.
One minute.
Cliff. Cliff. What's wrong?
Don't worry.
Everything's all right.
Oh, I can't tell you how
glad I am you took my case.
Cliff, you're doing
great in there, just great.
Now, in your cross...
Ben. Ben. Ben,
this has gotta stop.
Please, could you just butt out?
- Butt out?
- I know you're trying to help in there,
and I really appreciate it,
but you gotta let me
make my own mistakes.
Not that I wanna make mistakes.
But if I do, well, that's
how I'm gonna learn.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
You're right.
It's your case.
Win or lose.
Win or lose. Right.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'll just, uh, butt out.
Oh. You don't have to leave.
- I can stay?
- Yes, you can stay.
You just have to
sit in the back row.
Proceed.
Dr. Levinson, have any of your
patients ever come to you and said:
"I want a smaller nose
so I can get a better job"?
Or "I need a tummy tuck so
my husband won't leave me"?
Have they ever said that?
Anyone? No. Never.
- Never?
- I screen my patients very carefully.
If anyone comes to my office
expecting that a little plastic
surgery's gonna somehow solve
all their personal problems, I
show them right out the door.
So in other words, you
only operate on people
with realistic expectations,
who don't appear to
be neurotic in any way.
- That's correct.
- People like my client.
- Heh, well...
- You did operate on her, didn't you?
Uh, yes, but she...
So in your opinion, she's a
rational, emotionally stable woman.
- Is that correct?
- She was before the surgery. Yes.
Very interestingly put, doctor.
Very interestingly put.
You stated earlier that
you moved your practice
from Dallas to Atlanta
18 months ago. Why?
I felt like it.
Oh, it didn't have
anything to do with the fact
that the people in Dallas
were starting to sue you
with what would be termed
an annoying frequency?
Objection.
- Relevancy.
- Sustained.
Dr. Levinson, is it true that
during your last two years in Dallas,
five malpractice suits
were brought against you?
- Yes. But I had...
- No further questions, Your Honor.
- Ms. Simpson?
- Redirect, Your Honor.
Proceed.
Were any of these five suits
settled out of court, doctor?
No, they all went to trial.
They all went before juries
such as this one. Is that correct?
That's correct.
What was the outcome of
those trials, Dr. Levinson?
The jury found in my
favor in every single case.
Thank you. No further questions.
Sorry to have to
bring you in this late.
My life has been a
little hectic these days.
So I heard.
Jury still out?
Well, my attorney says the longer
they're out, the better it is for me.
Let's see this.
Well?
Well,
you tell me.
You're some kind of
genius, you know that?
Wait a minute. Whoa,
what are you doing?
Well, uh, how about a smile?
I'm gonna take a
little picture, you know.
I want it to go with the one
I took before the operation.
All right. Well,
okay, just one, okay?
One's all I need.
I can't believe it.
You look just like him.
Well, that was the
whole idea, wasn't it?
Yeah, but, Rod, I
mean, this is incredible.
From now on,
just call me Justin.
And you just call me Daddy.
I can't believe it.
In the case of
Westmore v. Levinson,
we, the jury, find for the
defendant, Dr. Albert Levinson.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
This court is adjourned.
I'm really sorry.
I could file an appeal for you
or you could get another lawyer.
No!
Get her off me.
Grab her arm. Grab her arm.
Get her off, come on.
Grab her arm. MAN 3: Hey.
Hi.
Mr. Greenwood. Did
you have an appointment?
Uh, no, I didn't, but something's
going on with my nose.
It just... It kind of
hurts right up in here.
It might be an infection. Come
on back and I'll take a look.
Oh, no offense, miss, but I'd much
rather have the main man look at it.
I understand. Have a seat. He
just called from the courthouse,
and he said he'd be
here in about 20 minutes.
Something wrong?
I just hadn't seen your face since
you had surgery. It looks good.
- You must be pleased.
- You have no idea.
Oh, by the way, do you happen
to know who owns that red Beretta
- that's always parked by the elevator?
- Yeah, I do.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
Well, just as I was getting on
the elevator to come up here,
- I saw somebody back into it.
- No, not again.
Have a seat. I'll be right back.
Sorry about that.
- Hey, hey, hey. JUDY:
Hey, congratulations.
- Another win for you.
- Ha, ha.
Levinson, six.
Fruitcakes, nothing.
- Oh. What...?
- Oh, yeah, she was a bad loser,
tried to take my
face off with her nails.
Let me put peroxide on that.
You know, when I was coming in,
I thought I saw Rod
Greenwood driving out.
Yeah, you did. He wanted
you to look at his nose.
He was having some sort
of postoperative discomfort.
- His nose?
- Mm-hm.
He shouldn't have any
problems with his nose.
- Let me see his chart. Here.
- Okay.
- That's odd.
- What?
His pre- and post-op
pictures are gone.
You sure they were there?
Yeah, you can see the
holes where I stapled them.
You know, Mr. Greenwood told
me somebody backed into my car.
I went down, but it
was somebody else's.
And when I got back
up here, he was gone.
Do you think he stole them?
Why would he do
something like that?
Another nutcase. Who knows?
Give him a call tomorrow.
Tell him I want to see him.
Mm.
- Morning.
- Hi, come on in. Have breakfast.
No, thanks.
Get to Page 7 yet?
Oh, you didn't learn
anything after that first ad?
It's not an ad.
It's worse.
Hmm.
Not only do I
lose my first case,
but the gory details wind
up in the morning paper.
Well, did Ms.
Westmore calm down?
Yeah. The movie
seemed to do the trick.
- Movie?
- Yeah.
- I took her to a movie after dinner.
- Dinner?
I took her out for a bite to
eat. It was the least I could do.
Oh.
At least it's over.
Have some breakfast.
No.
Have some eggs,
sausage, grits, pancakes.
I got a pot of baked beans with
hot dogs and onions cut up in them.
Mm, good.
No, Ben. No, I can't.
I gotta go to the courthouse.
Jackie... Uh, Ms. Westmore wants
me to make a motion for a new trial.
You're not.
Well, I gotta at least try.
- See you later.
- Hmm.
I think you're gonna
be very happy.
- I hope so.
- And I'll see you next week.
Thank you, doctor.
The information Rod
Greenwood gave us is phony.
- What do you mean, phony?
- The address and phone number
on the forms he
filled out don't exist.
- He lied?
- He must have.
Do you think he's in
some sort of trouble?
I mean, he paid
cash for everything.
Maybe he's trying to
get away from an ex-wife.
Or he's a criminal
looking for a new face.
Maybe we should call the police.
Let's not.
I mean, after
all, he did pay us.
Those cameras that security uses
to keep an eye on the parking garage,
are they connected to recorders?
Yeah, they are.
That's how they caught the guy
that nabbed my car last month.
Good.
It's open.
Hello?
Be right there, Billy boy.
Help yourself to a beer.
I haven't slept
this late since...
What the hell are
you doing here?
Who's this Justin Kerns?
You'd better leave.
- Why'd you wanna look like him?
- I said, leave.
Why did I have to
trace your license plate
- to figure out where you lived?
- Get out of here.
I wanna know
what's going on here.
It doesn't concern you,
doctor. Now, get out of here.
Go away and stay away.
Damn it.
- The police are searching her house.
- The police are searching your house?
Oh, it was horrible watching them
tear through my things like that.
Oh, I just had to
leave the house.
Thank God I was
able to reach Cliff.
I told the police
she'd be over here.
- They had a warrant?
- Oh, yeah.
They think I'm a murderer.
Just because you
threatened Dr. Levinson
and a few people
happened to see.
Threatened?
She was beating the
living hell out of him
and there was a gang watching.
Well, I was angry.
Anyone would've been.
But I got over it.
By bedtime that
night, I was fine.
- Wasn't I, Cliff?
- I beg your pardon?
Oh. Oh, no, we went
to dinner and a movie.
No, what she means is
by the time I dropped her off
to go to bed, she was fine.
- I see.
- We had had such a good time.
I forgot about that fiend
and what he had done to me.
Oh, we did have a good
time, didn't we, Cliff?
- Oh.
- Ha, ha.
We had a wonderful time.
I could never have gotten
through all this without him.
You're so sweet.
I think I will go into the kitchen
and get us some lemonade.
Dad, would you like to help?
- Um...
- Oh, no, no, you stay.
Dad's up.
What is going on in there?
That woman is all over him.
Yeah, I saw that.
She's his client.
What do you want
me to do about it?
Dad, this woman
is a little nuts,
and Cliff doesn't have a lot
of experience in a lot of ways,
if you know what I mean.
No. He doesn't.
You always know exactly what
to say to make me feel better.
Oh, excuse me. I
better go get that.
All right.
Mr. Lewis, I believe you indicated
I could find Ms. Westmore here.
Yes. She's right here. Jackie?
What's going on?
Mrs. Westmore, we've just
found what we're pretty sure
is the murder weapon
in your garage.
- What? CAVALLO: A
blood-stained scalpel
wrapped up in a towel with a
pair of latex gloves in a bucket
with some old rags.
Oh. Why, I never put them there.
Of course you didn't.
Well, we can talk
about that downtown
after Sergeant Donnelly
here reads you your rights.
Oh, Cliff.
Uh, just go with them.
I'll be right there. I'll be right behind.
It's okay. I'll be right behind you.
Cliff, you're the only
one I can depend on.
- I'll be there.
- Promise?
I promise.
Anything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
Say you'll help me.
Uh, no, I don't think
it's a good idea.
What do you want me to
do? Just bail out on her?
She'd be devastated.
Cliff, I don't think
you're aware of this,
but that woman is very
emotionally attached to you.
You're playing with fire.
Then help me.
Mother. SARAH: Ah!
Oh, damn it, Melanie,
don't startle me like that.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
Look what you've done.
My heart is just racing.
My head feels like it's about
to float off my shoulders.
Well, here, I picked up your
refills. Maybe you ought to take one.
The people that were going to cater
the reception called me this morning.
They said you decided
to go with someone else.
Yes, I found someone
who's cheaper.
For God's sakes,
Mother, this is my wedding.
I don't want whoever's
cheapest. I want the best.
Don't you want the best for me?
If you think I'm going to spend
a fortune on your wedding,
knowing full well your marriage
won't last out the year, think again.
How can you say that?
Because I know
you and I know Bill.
You don't love each other. You
just like the way you look together.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh, you're two peas in a pod.
You'll tear each other apart
trying to get what you want.
You don't know
how to love, Melanie.
You and Bill will never come close
to having what your father and I had.
Ever.
He hated you, Mother.
He absolutely hated you.
That is not true.
How's your pulse?
Is it back to normal?
Yes.
Those pills work like magic.
Good. Well, um, I've
gotta get back to work.
I didn't mean what
I said just now.
I guess I'm just, um, nervous
about the wedding, that's all.
The night janitor found
him lying there about 9:30.
Thank God he
found him and not me.
I can certainly understand that.
I had left the office
early, I guess about 4.
Dr. Levinson wasn't here.
He was gone somewhere.
Is it true that his
face was all cut up?
Yes. That's why the police were
so quick to call it an act of revenge.
How can you defend someone
who would do something like this?
Mrs. Westmore didn't do it.
And even if she had, she'd
still be entitled to an attorney.
Did Dr. Levinson
have any relatives?
Yeah. A sister in California.
How about ex-wives, girlfriends?
His wife died about two years ago,
and he hadn't been out with anyone since.
- So he was pretty much alone, then?
- Yeah, alone.
Was he troubled or
upset about anything?
Did he get a phone
call, a letter, anything?
I don't think so.
Was there anything at all unusual
that happened prior to his death?
The thing with Rod
Greenwood was sort of unusual.
In fact, that's the last
time I saw the doctor,
was when he left the
office to go talk to him.
- Rod Greenwood. Is that a patient?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, Dr. Levinson
did some work on me.
It's nice.
Well, thank you.
I mean, I didn't know you before
Dr. Levinson worked on you,
but you really can't even tell.
I thought he did a good job.
- Did you ever have, um...?
- Not yet.
I didn't think so.
You don't need it.
Well, thank you.
I understand
Dr. Levinson came by here.
No. Uh-uh.
I mean, I never saw him, anyway.
- You stopped by his office?
- Yeah.
The nurse said you
left unexpectedly.
Well, I hung out for a while,
he didn't show, and so I left.
Dr. Levinson and his nurse discovered
that your before-and-after pictures
from your file were missing.
Did you take them?
Why would I do that?
The nurse also
says that the address
and phone number
you gave were phony.
Has this woman got a
problem with me or something?
I paid all my bills, I
kept my appointments.
Why in the hell would
I lie about where I live?
I don't know.
Well, you know, maybe
Dr. Levinson's nurse just, uh...
Maybe she lost my
address or got it mixed up.
May I ask you something?
Why did you have all
that surgery done anyway?
Because I hated
the way I looked.
And now I love it.
Men can be vain too, you know.
Well, I've taken up
too much of your time.
I enjoyed it.
Oh.
Just one more question.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Anything.
Where you last night
from, say, 6 to 10?
Well, uh, I was with a friend,
just, uh, drinking beer
and barbecuing steaks.
Why did you tell her
you were with me?
I needed an alibi. What
was I supposed to say?
- Oh, you killed him?
- No, Billy boy, I thought you did.
No, wasn't me.
Well, surely you're not suggesting
that Miss Melanie here did it, are you?
I guess none of us did.
Just knowing someone's snooping
around has just got me nervous.
I mean, maybe we
should just hold off a while.
Oh, no, no, no, Billy boy.
I can't hang around
here looking like this.
What's one more week?
My mother gets more
insufferable by the day.
If we wait another
week, I'll probably blow,
and she'll end up
disinheriting me.
Uh-uh. We gotta get going.
Okay.
Sarah.
It's your fault I'm dead, Sarah.
He hated you.
He hated you. He
absolutely hated you.
Absolutely hated you.
My only daughter's getting
married, and I won't be there.
All because of you.
You drove me to my grave, Sarah.
I'm not going to rest till I do
the very same to you, Sarah.
Well, that doesn't necessarily
mean she called him that night.
Oh, I see. Okay.
I'll tell him. Thanks.
Thanks. Bye.
- Who was that?
- Detective Cavallo.
Oh, so Ms. Westmore.
This is not gonna
make Cliff happy.
Ben.
In the kitchen.
Speak of the devil.
I've got some bad news.
Bad news? LEANNE: Yes.
- Detective Cavallo called...
- Morning.
Morning. CLIFF: Morning.
My arraignment's today,
and Cliff stopped by.
He's so concerned.
I made cheese crepes.
- Which were to die for.
- Ha, ha.
He's, um, uh... What's
the best way of saying?
Fueled up.
Oh, he's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I don't know what
I'd do without him.
What did the police say?
Maybe you two should sit down.
Yeah. Cliff, you sit over here, and
you sit over here, out of the draft.
Mrs. Westmore, since
you're here, I was wondering,
did you make any
calls from your home
the night Dr. Levinson
was murdered?
- I don't think so.
- You sure?
Uh, well, no, no, I didn't.
I knew Cliff was working on my
appeal, and who else would I have called?
Apparently, Dr. Levinson was
wearing one of those beepers
that stores numbers
when people call.
It indicates that one of the calls
he got that night was from you.
I never called him.
He was the last
person I would call.
The district attorney considers it
additional proof that you're the killer.
Well, how does
that prove anything?
Well, the district
attorney believes
that you called and left
your number on his beeper
so that when he returned your
call, you could make arrangements
to meet him and, uh, khh.
I never made that call. You
believe me, don't you, Cliff?
Of course I do. Of course I do.
Anybody could've called Dr. Levinson
and left her number on his beeper.
It's not proof.
Not solid proof, anyway.
I appreciate your coming
on such short notice.
It was very nice
of you to do that.
- Mother?
- Thank you very much.
What's going on?
- Who's that? SARAH:
Someone from Korbel Realty.
I forget her name.
- I decided to sell the house.
- Why?
We've been through this before,
Melanie. It's my house now.
- I get to do with it whatever I please.
- But you love this house.
Just last week, you
said you'd never sell it.
Well, I changed my mind. - Why?
- I just did! That's all.
- I'm not leaving until you tell me why.
Your father was here last night.
I woke up out of a sound sleep, and
he was standing at the foot of the bed.
Heh. Mother, you were dreaming.
- No.
He was there, and he said...
He said things to me.
He said terrible things.
I've never been so
scared in all my life,
and my heart, it was
pounding so hard it hurt.
And then I tried to take my
pills, but they weren't there.
- The ones I just brought you?
- He kept coming toward me,
and then he touched me.
And his hands were like ice.
And the next thing I knew, I was
lying on the floor, and he was gone.
I couldn't get to sleep
the rest of the night.
I just can't stay in this house
anymore. I just have to sell it.
Mother, listen to me.
You were dreaming.
- There is no ghost.
- It was not a dream.
Mother, please, Father's been
dead for more than two months.
Why didn't this ghost of
his appear sooner, hmm?
- Why did it wait until last night?
- I don't know.
Because there is
no ghost, that's why.
It was just a dream.
Now, come on, let's
go find those pills.
Just a few more
reps and I'll be done.
- A few more what?
- Reps.
- Short for repetitions.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
All these pictures are of you.
Yep, that's right.
I'm a model.
- Ever have plastic surgery?
- No, heh.
I don't intend to, either.
That's why I do this.
What do you think
about Rod Greenwood
having all that plastic surgery?
Rod?
Huh.
- You didn't know?
- No.
Then again, it's not like
we're best friends or anything.
- Do you want a mineral water?
- No, thanks.
Uh, wait a minute, I
am a little thirsty. Um...
Um, what's that?
Oh, that's a
concentrated protein drink.
Oh.
- How about that?
- Asparagus juice.
Oh.
- Tap water will do.
- All right.
So how'd you and Rod
Greenwood get to be friends?
Oh, I met him in,
uh, a softball league.
Only known him a couple
of weeks. There you go.
Oh, thanks. What'd he do?
Some kind of aerospace
engineer or something.
- Just got laid off.
- Hmm.
Huh.
Ah.
Well, thanks for the
water and for talking to me.
You're a big help, big.
Uh, what do you mean?
- What do you mean, what do I mean?
- I just mean, what do you mean?
Oh, I just mean that every little bit of
information counts, that's all I mean.
- Well, I'll let you get back to your reps.
- Reps.
- Reps. Ha, ha.
- Ha, ha.
- I'll remember that.
- See you.
- Aerospace engineer?
- Well, I had to call him something.
I mean, "two-bit hood" didn't
have quite the right ring to it.
Hmm.
- Who are you calling?
- Rod.
- Oh, he's not at home.
- And how do you know?
Heh, because he's never at
home at 5:00 in the afternoon.
He runs in the park.
Honestly, Bill, you
can be so unobservant.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
Make sure he knows
that this is his last chance.
All right.
Tell him to ice his
whole body this time.
Whatever it takes
to get it right.
What's up?
The partner of that lady
you talked to yesterday,
Ben Matlock, came by to see me.
Yeah? What'd you tell him?
Told him we'd met
on a softball team.
Told him you were some
kind of aerospace engineer.
- They can check that, man.
- What was I supposed to say?
Think! That's what
you're supposed to do!
You're supposed to think! God.
Bill Parker's a vegetarian?
Yeah, he's a vegetarian.
He had all those meatless cookbooks,
and I looked in his refrigerator,
there's no meat in there,
not even a piece of bologna,
just oranges and apples and
carrots and squash and juice
and stuff like belonged
to some kind of big rabbit.
- So, what do you think?
- What do you think I think?
You think Rod Greenwood
was lying about going over there
for a steak barbecue the night
Dr. Levinson was murdered.
And guess what?
Mr. Parker, I followed him,
and the man he was talking to in the
park looked exactly like Justin Kerns.
- Justin Kerns.
- That's that businessman
that I used to know, died
a couple of months ago.
Right, I remember, had a stroke.
Anyway, this guy
looked exactly like him.
I swear, Leanne, it
was like seeing a ghost.
Well, you know what they say:
Somewhere everybody's got a double.
He's Justin Kerns' double,
and he was real nervous.
He kept looking around,
wringing his hands,
and he'd talk loud
every now and then.
- I was too far to hear.
- Huh.
And he started
chewing on a toothpick.
- It was habit, I guess.
- That's funny.
Rod Greenwood
chews on a toothpick.
Shake it.
What are you doing?
I wanna show you something.
- Recognize him?
- Yeah. Rod Greenwood.
No. Justin Kerns.
You think Rod Greenwood had
Dr. Levinson do plastic surgery on him
so he'd look like Justin Kerns?
- Hmm.
- Ah.
Why would somebody
wanna look like a dead man?
I don't know.
Oh.
Dad, you know, it's late. Maybe
we should do this tomorrow.
No. She's still up, see?
No! Justin, no!
Mrs. Kerns?
Dad, you go this
way, I'll go this way.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Come on. I broke in.
Mrs. Kerns? Hello?
Hello?
Mrs. Kerns?
Uh, ahem.
Woo-hoo.
- Hello?
- Mrs. Kerns!
Hello?
Mrs. Kerns?
Mrs. Kerns!
Anybody home?
Anybody here?
Mrs. Kerns? LEANNE: Hello?
What was that?
Is that Mrs. Kerns?
It was.
She's dead.
Medical examiner says it
looks like a heart attack, Ben.
I'm telling you, somebody
was up here with her.
We heard her yell at somebody
right before we found her.
We heard a door slam downstairs
like somebody was leaving.
- Oh, no, no.
- Oh, Elena.
Mrs. Kerns is dead?
It's her heart.
Oh, I should've
come home sooner.
No. You couldn't have
done anything. She, um...
She tried to take a
pill, but it was too late.
Excuse me, Miss Kerns, your
mother was on medication?
Mm-hm, for cardiac arrhythmia.
That's what was in her hand.
I see. It was a heart attack.
I'm telling you, Steve,
somebody was up here with her.
We heard her screaming,
and that's why we broke in.
But you didn't see anyone. - No.
- He must have come back.
- Elena, stop it.
- Who must have come back?
- Mr. Kerns.
Mrs. Kerns said he came
to her the other night.
Seeing him again must
have been too much for her.
Mrs. Kerns thought she
saw her dead husband?
It was just this dream she had.
Well, maybe not.
So she was up here with a
ghost when the two of you arrived?
Not a ghost, a real
person, Rod Greenwood.
Rod Greenwood had plastic
surgery done by Dr. Albert Levinson
- so he would look like Justin Kerns.
- Dr. Levinson's tied up in this?
That's why we came here,
so we could talk to Mrs. Kerns,
- see if she knew anything about it.
- Maybe I'd better have a talk
- with Rod Greenwood.
- Come on.
I'm not sure what we'll
find, but it's worth checking.
You know the way?
Okay. I'll meet you
at Greenwood's motel.
Hmm.
- Wait a minute.
- What?
I saw this car in Bill
Parker's driveway yesterday.
Mr. Greenwood?
Mr. Greenwood.
Do you happen to know
if he was home today?
Beats me.
You're sure that's him?
That's Rod Greenwood, all right.
All his things are gone.
He never said anything
to me about moving out.
If you hear from him,
let me know. You too.
Yeah.
There. Father's things go to the church
and Mother's things go to the shelter.
Yes, ma'am, I'll take
care of it right away.
Allow me.
Whew.
Very nice.
Goes with your new car.
You shouldn't be here.
Someone might see you.
Maid's gone. Billy
boy's flexing his pecs.
I knew you'd be alone.
I still have my key.
Ah. Oh, no, no, no. Uh-uh.
You're supposed to be in hiding.
I got bored.
And a little broke.
I need another 20 grand.
I don't have any money, not
until the estate gets out of probate.
- Borrow it.
- That wasn't our deal.
Okay.
Let's see, then. Uh...
Why don't we hawk
some of this stuff?
For your information,
the cops are onto you.
And so is that lawyer Matlock.
So if I were you, I'd crawl
under a rock and stay there
until this whole thing cools
down, just like we planned.
You're forgetting
something, pretty little doll.
The closer they get to me,
the closer they get to you.
I want that money.
All right.
Come back tomorrow
night and I'll have it for you.
Of course, it's not like money
is the only thing I'm interested in.
Oh, that can probably
be arranged too.
Good.
Good morning.
Excuse me. You're in my chair.
- I am?
Tradition. The lead attorney
always sits in the middle.
- He does?
- Yes, Cliff, he does.
Detective Cavallo, I
show you this scalpel,
people's exhibit H, which the
defense has stipulated is the weapon
that killed Dr. Levinson.
Do you recognize it?
Yes, sir. I do. It has my mark.
Did you find this scalpel?
- Yes, I did.
Wrapped in a bloody towel
in the defendant's garage.
Somebody put that in my
garage. Can't you do something?
Not now, honey. Don't
worry. It'll be all right.
Aw.
Ahem. Ben, uh... Ben thought
that you and I should have this talk.
About what? How
he's blowing my case?
Oh, no, no, no. He's not...
No, he's not blowing your case.
Oh, honestly, Cliff, I'd feel so
much better if you were in charge.
He's got so much more
experience than I do.
Experience? Experience?
I mean, he does
everything by rote.
He lacks your youthful
exuberance and passion.
Just because he has a track
record. I mean, what's that?
That doesn't mean
he's better than you are.
No. Oh, no, no, no. See,
no, no, you know what? This...
Jackie, this is exactly the kind of
thing that we have to talk about.
Uh, ahem. I get the feeling,
as does Ben, as
does everyone else,
that you're, um...
I don't know how to say
this. That you're, uh...
- You're fond of me.
- Fond of you?
Cliff, I'm in love with you,
head over heels
in love with you.
Oh.
No, no, no, that's not good
either. No, no, that's worse.
Well, I can't help what I feel.
Well, I'm your attorney. We
have a professional relationship.
The fact... Thank you very much.
The fact of the matter is,
I'm not gonna have a personal
relationship with you right now.
It's unethical. It's
unprincipled. It's wrong.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Oh, a man of principle.
Ooh, you have no idea
how that turns me on.
Jackie. Jackie.
I understand. I
understand. All right.
I promise, from now on,
I'll keep my feelings in
check and my hands to myself.
Okay.
But the instant
the trial is over,
you are mine.
Check, please.
Melanie! MELANIE:
Up here in the bedroom!
What the hell happened here?
You were interrupted
the night that Mother died,
so you came back
tonight to finish the job.
But this time I interrupted you.
Only I had a gun.
Melanie, what are you doing?
I enjoyed you for a while,
but I had to stop you from
committing this robbery.
Oh, come on, baby.
Come on, you're no killer.
That's my job, remember?
Yes, help me, please! Oh, God.
I just shot somebody, and I
think I might have killed him.
I came by so I could pick up
more clothes to take to the shelter
first thing in the morning.
But when I turned on the light,
he was standing next to the
bed, holding Mother's jewelry box.
And I screamed, and
then he came towards me,
so I pulled the gun out of
my purse and I shot him.
You, uh, carry a
gun in your purse?
It's my fiancé's idea.
He wants me to be
able to defend myself.
When I saw his face, I
thought I shot my father.
You wouldn't think plastic
surgery could do that.
We won't know for sure
until we run some prints,
but I'll bet that that
is Rod Greenwood.
Poor Mother.
She really thought
she saw a ghost.
Did either of your parents
know Rod Greenwood?
No. Not at all.
Why would someone
wanna change his face
so he could look like my father?
I really don't know.
Do you mind if my men and
I have a look around here?
Oh, no. Uh, please,
by all means.
- Ben?
- Kitchen!
- Ben.
- Hmm?
The police found
threatening letters.
Threatening letters?
Yeah. They were locked inside
Justin Kerns' desk, unsigned.
They think they're
from Rod Greenwood?
Well, they were written by
someone who accused Justin Kerns
of having an affair
with their mother.
I don't know.
They were angry,
and they said that the
family was destroyed
and the parents got divorced,
and, well, eventually, the
mother committed suicide.
Rod Greenwood's
mother kill herself?
Well, yeah, as a
matter of fact, she did,
right before the
letters were written.
I can't figure out why
he changed his face.
I don't know.
- Maybe, um... May I?
- Yeah.
Maybe to scare her to death,
you know, or to get revenge
while he was stealing
the family jewels,
which is what he was doing when
Melanie Kerns shot him to death.
Hmm.
That's, um...
That's weird, isn't it?
Yeah. It's really weird.
Oh, um...
By the way, I had that little
talk with Mrs. Westmore.
- Good.
- I don't think it really went that well.
I don't think that
she, you know, um...
Sumptuous. Just sumptuous.
So this is all yours now.
- Yeah, I guess.
- Yeah.
Yours and Bill Parker.
- We're getting married next May.
- Oh, I heard. I heard.
That, uh... Ahem.
That old BMW that I saw
parked in his driveway is yours.
I mean, it used to be before
you got the new one out there.
- It's a beauty.
- Thanks.
- Uh, did you know Rod Greenwood?
- No, I didn't.
Well, Bill did.
Is that possible?
I don't know.
He never did tell you
that Rod Greenwood looked
exactly like your father?
As a matter of fact, he did tell me
once that he met a guy playing softball
who looked a lot like Dad,
but I didn't think much of it.
Huh. No, I guess not, huh?
You know, sometimes my
job just bores me to death.
I just hate to ask
all these questions.
But I have to find out who
actually killed Albert Levinson.
Of course. When
did he die, again?
It was the 17th, a Thursday,
between 6 and 9 p.m.
The maid has Thursday nights
off, so when Mother was alive,
- I used to keep her company.
- So you would have been here then.
Yes.
- Poor Mother.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
Well, hi to Bill, and
good luck with all this.
Just sumptuous. Sumptuous.
Damn it, Melanie, why
did you have to kill him?
Because he was
blackmailing us. Relax, Bill.
Oh, relax. Right.
Oh, God.
I mean, Ben Matlock
knows we're engaged.
He knows I knew Rod.
He knows Rod's responsible
for your mother's death.
He knows you inherit everything.
This whole thing's falling apart.
Ben Matlock is not a cop.
And even if he were,
he can't prove anything.
Now, just take it easy.
The only thing that's
falling apart is you.
Well, maybe I should
just get out of town.
Oh. That's a good idea.
That'll make you look
real innocent, won't it?
I just don't have the stomach
for this kind of thing. You like it.
I mean, you get a rush from
living on the edge. I don't.
We're in this together, kiddo.
And as long as we
both remember that,
everything will be fine.
Hi, I'm Ben
Matlock, an attorney.
I was here the night
Mrs. Kerns, you know...
Well, what are you
doing out there?
Oh, just poking around.
I do that a lot.
I saw you in here, and I thought
maybe we could talk a while,
if you got time.
- I suppose.
- Okay.
Terrible thing that
happened to Mrs. Kerns.
How long had she been
having heart trouble?
- Couple of years.
- Mm-hm.
The night she died,
was that your night off?
Yeah. Thursdays
are my night off.
I understand that
usually on Thursdays,
you go to your daughter's house.
- Most of the time.
We just heard
Dr. Levinson's nurse testify
that a few months
prior to his murder,
he performed plastic surgery on
a man named Rod Greenwood,
made him look just
like your late father.
Did you know Rod Greenwood?
- No.
Did you ever see Rod Greenwood?
Yes. MATLOCK: When?
I caught him burglarizing
my mother's house.
I shot him to death
in self-defense.
How did your mother die?
- Heart attack.
The police are fairly
certain that Rod Greenwood
got into her house
and surprised her,
and the shock of seeing what
she thought was my father's ghost
was apparently too
much for her heart.
She suffered from arrhythmia.
Oh.
So the police think
that Rod Greenwood
had plastic surgery done
so he could look like your father
and scare your mother to death.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
- Who inherits her estate?
- I do.
Any idea how much it's worth?
Somewhere between
20 and 30 million dollars.
That's a lot of money,
even when you say it fast.
Makes me kind of think
that maybe, just maybe,
you did know Rod Greenwood,
and maybe, just maybe,
you convinced him to
transform himself into your father,
knowing the sight of him would
scare your mother to death.
Objection. Calls for speculation,
assumes facts not in evidence.
Sustained. Mr. Matlock.
What's the matter with that?
You heard Mr. Lane.
Speculation assumes
facts not in evidence?
That's what he said.
Well, I said, it kind
of makes me think.
If I have to count to three...
Miss Kerns, uh,
why would you say Rod Greenwood
wanted to scare your mother to death?
For revenge.
The police found threatening
letters apparently from him
locked away in your
father's desk, didn't they?
- Yes.
- Mm-hm.
This is one of those letters.
Have you ever seen it before?
- Yes.
- Did Rod Greenwood ever tell you
that his mother
committed suicide?
I told you that I
didn't know him.
- Then how did you write these
letters? LANE: Objection. No foundation.
Sustained. Mr. Matlock,
would you care to
make an offer of proof?
Uh, ahem, Your Honor,
I can't prove this witness
actually wrote these letters.
But I do know for a fact they
were not written three years ago
as they're dated.
Hold this letter against the light
and read the watermark on the paper.
"Finley Bond 7."
According to Finley Paper
Company, their Number 7 bond paper
was first produced
three months ago.
So how do you think
these letters got typed
and placed in your father's den?
- I have no idea. MATLOCK:
And are you aware
that your father's brokerage
firm, where you work,
uses Finley bond paper?
And you did know Rod
Greenwood, didn't you?
If these questions are
uncomfortable, try this.
- Did you know Dr. Albert Levinson?
- No.
- Ever go to his office?
His office is in a medical
building at 1903 West Selby.
Ever go there? MELANIE: No.
You used to drive
a Silver 1984 BMW,
license plate
BKO248, did you not?
Yes. MATLOCK: Mm-hm.
Uh...
This photograph was taken off a tape
that was made by a security camera
in the parking garage
at 1903 West Selby.
See, right here.
Seven forty-nine p.m. the 17th.
Anyway, at the time
Dr. Levinson was murdered,
the night he was murdered,
the approximate
time he was murdered,
your car was parked in the
parking garage beneath his office.
- That is your car, isn't it?
- Yes, but...
Albert Levinson grew
suspicious of Rod Greenwood,
and in order to keep
your plan on track,
you killed him
and made it look like Jackie
Westmore had done it, didn't you?
- No.
- Where were you that night?
I was at my mother's.
No. Try again.
Your mother's maid, Elena,
didn't sleep over at her
daughter's house that night.
Her daughter had the flu.
So Elena stayed home,
and she's prepared to testify
that you were nowhere near
your mother's house that night.
You were afraid that Dr. Levinson
would wreck the whole thing.
If he spilled the beans,
your mother would make sure
that you never
inherited a penny.
So you killed him, didn't you?
Where were you, Melanie?
I was at the Parkside Hotel.
- Say again?
- I was at the Parkside Hotel.
Would you like to see
my credit card receipt?
Anybody see you there?
Yes, uh, a maid.
She walked into my room
while I was preoccupied.
- Who were you with?
- It's none of your business.
You were with Rod
Greenwood, weren't you?
Mm, mm, mm.
Well, this is the
capper, isn't it?
This caps the capper.
Sleeps with a man
that looks like her father,
and then she kills him.
Yep. Caps the stack.
When I think of all the times
that you accused me of being wild,
heh, I was a piece
of milquetoast.
You had your times.
Okay, so if Melanie was with
Rod Greenwood that night,
- she didn't kill Dr. Levinson.
- No.
- Guess Mr. Greenwood didn't either.
- Guess not.
- Guess that leaves one.
- Yep.
What was in this box
that was next to the body?
Well, let's see, he was, um...
He'd just gotten a bunch of samples
from a pharmaceutical company,
and he was putting them away
in that cupboard right there.
It's all here in
the police report.
They say one of the boxes was
empty. I guess it was this one.
- What's Dermazin?
- Skin ointment prescription.
Mostly for acne, but a lot of
people use it to get rid of wrinkles.
Oh, yeah.
I hear that you and Melanie Kerns
are engaged to be married, Mr. Parker.
- That's right.
- When's the big day?
Well, we're not
quite sure right now.
Oh, that's right, she's
been arrested and charged
with Rod Greenwood's
murder, hasn't she?
- You must be very disappointed.
- I am.
- I love Melanie very much.
- And how about that $30 million
you were gonna
inherit along with her?
Saying goodbye to that
must have hurt a little too.
Well, I make plenty
of money as a model.
What we would or
wouldn't have inherited
was never a big deal to me.
Course, just cause you
make a lot of money now,
what about ten years from now?
Five years from
now? Tastes change.
People change.
Age creeps up on men
just like it does on women.
I mean, look at me.
So that 30 million would
have made quite a soft landing
in case you had to fall back
on something else, wouldn't it?
I never gave it much thought.
Huh.
I understand that you and
Rod Greenwood were friends.
Acquaintances.
I knew him from a softball
league we both played in.
Kind of got a kick out of how much
he looked like Melanie's old man.
Did you know him
before the plastic surgery
that made him look like that?
No, I didn't.
Oh, come on, now.
You must have met him
somewhere and realized
that he's not what you'd
call an upstanding citizen
and talked him into
becoming Justin Kerns
so that you and Melanie could
use him to kill Sarah Kerns
and inherit that $30 million.
- No.
- You didn't pay to have him
do all that, pay his
medical expenses
using some of that big modeling
money you're talking about?
- No.
- Objection.
Sustained.
Your Honor, I'll move to
another line of questioning.
Thank you. Um...
I know you ride a
motorcycle, Mr. Parker.
Did you ever drive that old '84
BMW your fiancée used to own?
- Of course.
- Heh.
It must have been a hassle
borrowing the keys
from her all the time.
No. I had my own set.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, yeah.
So that's how her car
got in the parking lot
by Dr. Levinson's office.
She didn't drive
it there, you did.
No. I have no idea
how that car got there.
Oh, yeah, you drove it there.
You knew that Dr. Levinson
could blow your plan
to get your hands
on that 30 million,
so you drove the car
there, picked up a scalpel,
- stabbed him to death.
- No.
And when you saw
this in the paper,
you knew just who to frame.
- Jackie Westmore.
- That's not true.
You had everything you needed.
Just drive over to her
house, go in the garage,
take the scalpel, the gloves
you used to commit the murder,
throw them in that bucket,
used the telephone in the
garage to call Dr. Levinson's office,
leave her number on his beeper.
I was home all night.
I never left the house.
Okay. Okay.
Then how did this
wind up in your
medicine cabinet?
Yeah, I had a nice long talk with
Detective Cavallo this morning.
The upshot of it was he got a
warrant to search your house.
I told him to look
for this. He found it.
Would you tell the
good people what it is?
It's a tube of Dermazin.
- What's it for? BILL:
It gets rid of wrinkles.
My dermatologist gave it to me.
Hmm.
A box of Dermazin was found
on the floor by Dr. Levinson's body.
Apparently, he had been
stacking these away in a cabinet.
Some pharmaceutical company
had delivered them that afternoon.
The box on the floor was empty.
But it did have a
lot number on it.
It's right here in
the police report.
Would you just read
that number aloud?
It's lot number A76944.
Now read the lot number on the tube
that came from your medicine cabinet.
It's A76944.
The same. Your dermatologist
didn't give you this.
You saw it on the floor after you
had murdered Albert Levinson.
You thought:
"Well, nobody's ever gonna
miss this," so you stole it.
Greed, Mr. Parker.
And vanity.
Greed and vanity.
You can't let them get out of control.
They'll get the best of you every time.
What's ironic is that Dermazin is
not a sure-fire cure for wrinkles at all.
It can cause severe
redness and swelling,
and it makes your skin
extremely sensitive to the sun.
Oh, you've tried it?
Well, I think it's safe to say that I
have tried just about everything.
Thank you again,
Mr. Matlock. Mwah.
Well, Cliff.
Um, excuse us.
Well, I guess now
the trial's over,
we don't have a professional
relationship anymore, do we?
I guess not.
- Wanna go to lunch with me today?
- Oh, Cliff.
I've been thinking a lot since
we had that talk at dinner,
and, uh, well, dumb me,
I finally realized that
what I thought was love
wasn't really love at all.
My life was in turmoil, and,
well, you were my lifeline,
so I clung to you.
But I wasn't in love with you.
I met the most
marvelous plastic surgeon,
and when he's done,
he will have corrected all the
mistakes that monster made.
Oh. And then, Cliff, I am going
to the Caribbean for two weeks
and then maybe Cancun.
I guess you need a
vacation after all that.
Oh, darling Cliff, thank
you for understanding.
Mwah.
You will always be in my heart.
- Bye-bye. Bye.
- Bye.
Well... MATLOCK: Yeah.
- Looking for men.
- Well, what's the matter with me?
Too old.
- I'm too old for her?
- Yep.
She said she liked me.
I thought she meant it.
I figured for once in my
life, I had a sure thing.
Done deal, fait accompli.
How do I wind
up? Too old for her.
- I just don't get it.
- Well, just forget it, Cliff.
- Come to lunch with us.
- Really?
Hey, how about those personal
ads in the newspaper, you know?
Like "Shy young man seeks
outgoing woman, age unimportant."
No.
Don't even think about it.
www.tvsubtitles.net